{
    "id": "e445243e1a9c4108bd95332ea78340c6",
    "title": "Adverbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We will have to do something ………………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "quick",
                "quickly"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She danced……………………………. into the room.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "happy",
                "happily"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The fish was …………………………. cooked.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bad",
                "badly"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t remember him very ………………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "well"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "It is …………………………… hot today.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "terrible",
                "terribly"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She was driving …………………………… fast.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "unusual",
                "unusually"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I was ………………………….. in love with him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "mad",
                "madly"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I hate arriving ……………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "late",
                "lately"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He was ……………………….. punished for his crimes.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "just",
                "justly"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "My husband ………………………… forgot my birthday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "complete",
                "completely"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}